PALWASHA KHURSHID

Portfolio:

https://www.behance.net/palwashkhurshi

Phone: 03135706525

Email:

PalwashaJK12@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

I am a qualified and professional artist and teacher with a high level of experience and a real zest for sharing my passion for all things about art and teaching. You institute can be a great opportunity to represent my work and polish my skills.

EDUCATION —

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS| UNIVERSITY OF PESHAWAR2010 – 2012Member| Army Burn Hall AbotabadINTERMEDIATE| GOVT DEGREE COLLEGE FOR GIRLS2010

EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

• free lance • graphics •thumbnail templates • icon designing. Working with @zubairalikhan for Facebook, twitter and youtube thumbnails.

2015 - 2020

Teacher • Khan Children Academy • Trillium montisory education to children between the ages of 3 to 16 years.

2014 – 2015Interior design • Interior designer • Management assistant.

KEY SKILLS —

-Illustrations -Sketching- Interior designing _-proficient in adobe photo shop -Graphic design-Wall designing

CERTIFICATE

Sept 30 2015 -USAIDPAINTING CONTEST—Hazara University Havellian Campus Abotabad Nov 2022 -14NATIONAL CONVENTION SQCsPOSTER MAKING CONTEST—Honored to judge the contest

GRAPHIC DESIGN

-Game screen shot designing for play store-can design logos-can design multi graphic frames

HOBBIES

sketching – Instagram handle @art.by.palwashaDrawing – I draw graphite portraits